

Iqbal Fauzi

Backend Engineer - Web Developer

Contact Person



085232194153



Domicile

Iqbalfauzi100@gmail.com



Candi 3D Street, Karangbesuki, Sukun, Malang, East Java

About me

Hi! I am Fauzi from Malang city, Indonesia. I am backend engineer, stack currently on laravel framework. I have more than two vears experience at web PHP developing espesially at programming . and I start develop website since 2014th. Now I'm focus at laravel framework. ~ Fauzi

Softskills



Computer Skill

Laravel	60%
Codelgniter	90%
PHP Native	90%

Language

Indonesian	Active
	ı
English	Passive

Name Iqbal Fauzi

Place & DOB Bojonegoro, 7th April 1996

Occupation Web Developer - Freelancer

Religion Islam

Hobby Coding, Reading book, Swimming,

Malang

Height / Weight 170 cm / 60 kg

Work Experiences

Personal Data

Web Programmer Juli 2017 – Nop 2018 Build a website for Scholarship selection system, E- Tugas (assignments to new students of UIN Malang), and Tracer Application & database alumni System UIN Malang at The Office of Students and alumni affair of UIN Malang





Web Programmer February 2017-Mei 2017 Build a website at PTID UIN Malang. Pengembangan Teknologi Informasi dan Pangkalan Data (PTID) is a unit responsible for the management and development of information systems in the UIN Malang.

Internship December 2016-February 2017

Build a website complaining about service interruptions at PLN APD - East Java

Education

UIN Maulana Malik Ibrahim Malang



2014 - 2018 Informatic Engineering IPK 3,56 / 4,00

SMAN 1 Kalitidu-Bojonegoro



2011 - 2014 IPA Average 8,91 / 10